I thought that even if the five of us were in the same class, we would never all get along.
I didn't get to experience youth and adolescence with my friends.
So the five of us had a lot of fun together on this shoot, and it was a lot of fun to be able to bring out the five of us.
It was a lot of fun to be able to bring out the five of us.
It was so much fun to be able to show the five of us together.
I think this photo book is like a memory of the past.
Five young members of the idol group Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku release photo book
The five members enthusiastically talked about the highlights of the photo book, which is like a peek into their youth as students.
The five of us had a photo-free live performance, but it was the first time for all five of us to do a photo shoot together.
This was the first time for the five of us to do a photo shoot together.
In fact, it was so chaotic that I wondered if I could take the pictures.
I was worried about whether we would be able to take cute pictures.
But we had fun in the fun parts and made decisions in the decisive parts.
I think we were able to create a photo book that only the five of us could produce.
For me, it was the first time for the five of us to shoot together in uniforms like this.
We all had so much fun that we probably forgot that we were shooting.
It was the last time we wore the uniforms in our high school life.
To be honest, I'm glad we made it just in time.
The photobook was shot in various situations at school, such as in class and after school,
The photo book was shot in various situations at school, such as in class and after school.
It is full of shots that make you think what it would be like if the five of us were at the same school.
When I saw that photo book for the first time,
When I first saw the book, I was under the illusion that the five of us were all in the same class,
I think that this photo book is so natural that it is like a memory of the past.
I hope you will include them in your memories of the past.
It wasn't often that I got to shoot in such a summery, cute uniform, so I hope you will include them in your memories.
I didn't have many opportunities to shoot in such a cute summery uniform.
It was very fresh and fun.
When I was in junior high school
I was in junior high school when I joined Ebitu and had a lot of lessons.
I had a lot of things to do in junior high school
youth
I didn't experience youth with my friends so much
I didn't have the chance to experience youth with my friends.
So we had a lot of fun together
We had a lot of fun together.
It was a lot of fun to be able to bring out the five of us.
The year when we shot the photo book of the five of us
It was the only year when all five of us were in high school.
I'm very happy that we were able to do the photo book in that year.
I was very happy that we were able to shoot the book in that year.
I thought that even if the five of us were in the same class
I thought that even if the five of us were in the same class, we would never get along.
If the five of us were to have fun together, we would definitely ride our bicycles around on the way home, go for walks in various places, go to the beach, go shopping, eat, and so on.
I'd like to do things like that with the five of us, things that high school students would do.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku, celebrating their 15th anniversary, revealed their goals for the future.
Our goal was to stand at SSA as a group.
But it has been decided that we will be performing at Saitama Super Arena on March 20, 2025.
But my goal is not to reach the goal there.
My goal is to get more people to know and find me there.
My personal goal is to stand at Tokyo Dome, so I want to show that I am not going to stop yet.
My personal goal is to stand in Tokyo Dome, so I would like to show them that we are not going to stop yet.
The first official photo book with the five of us
It's the first official photo book of the five of us together.
It's really a nest of the five of us.
It's a photo book of the five of us
I hope you all enjoy it.
I hope you all will have a look at it.
JK
Coconut was the last photo shoot of JK.
The five of us have created a piece that fully expresses the sense of youth.
So please pick up a copy!
Five young members of the idol group Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
released a photobook!
A peek into the youth of their school days
Talking about the highlights of the photobook
TV Asahi AI announcer
TV Asahi AI announcer Yuina Hanazato reported
TV Asahi ai announcer Yuina Hanazato tells about the highlights of the photobook